

CHARAWUT PHONKUSON

Address: 71/120, Modiz, Soi Lat Phrao 18, Lat Phrao Rd. Chom Phon, Chatuchak, Bangkok, 10900 Date of Birth: July 10, 1997 Nationality: Thai Age: 24 Tel: 091-686-3076 Email: charawut 01@hotmail.com

BACKGROUND

I am currently a consultant (Technology-Cybersecurity) in the Consulting service at EY Thailand. I have experience in Personal Data Protection Act (PDPA) projects with clients in the food industry, FMCG industry, and state enterprise, Technology Risk Management project with clients in the banking industry and SAP GRC project with client in the Energy industry.

CAREER OBJECTIVE

I am looking for a new challenging opportunity, wish to use management and technology consulting, and financial economic analysis skills to help your company with the upcoming challenges.

EDUCATION

2016-2020

Chulalongkorn University, Bangkok, Thailand **Bachelor of Economics in Monetary Economics** GPAX: 3.32/4.00 (Graduated with Second-Class Honors)

QUALIFICATION

- Ability to work under pressure and time management
- Responsible, efficient, flexible and patience
- Competent at managing responsibilities in a highvolume atmosphere
- Hard worker, quick learner, and ability to assume responsibility
- Ability to build rapport
- Language Thai and English

2010-2015

Chumphae Suksa School, Khon Kaen, Thailand Science - Mathematics Program GPAX: 3.81/4.00 (Graduated)

TECHNICAL AND PERSONAL SKILLS

- Analyze and reason economic skill
- **Bloomberg (Bloomberg Market Concepts** Certificate)
- Microsoft Office (MS word, Power Point, Excel)
- Gretl, Stata, SPSS
- SAP GRC
- Personal Data Protection Act (PDPA)
- **Business Process Improvement**
- Project Management Essentials (Udemy)

EXTRACURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

- President of Plook Camp 2018 (mangrove planting) in Faculty of Economics
- Board of 72nd Chula–Thammasat Traditional Football (funding position) (2017)
- Creative operator of 3rd Thailand's Economics Students Assembly (TESA) (2017)
- Content operator of Economics Chulalongkorn University Expo 2017
- Treasurer operator of Plook Camp 2017 (mangrove planting) in Faculty of Economics
- Administration register of 19th Chulalongkorn Economics Quiz (2017)
- Volunteer of a rural development camp on behalf of the Faculty of Economics (2017)
- Chief of Liaison in 20th Chulalongkorn Khon kaen Camp (2017)

WORK EXPERIENCE

EY Thailand

Consultant, Technology-Cybersecurity, Consulting - Full-time (November 2020 - Present)

- Performed Personal Data Protection Act (PDPA) project for one of Thailand's largest food companies, a large FMCG multinational company, and a large Thai state enterprise, with including gap assessment, data inventory gap assessment, developing recording of processing data (ROPA), high-level data flow, and data privacy documents such as privacy policy, privacy notice, third party assessment checklists, data subject request, data breach incidence response plan, and training material packs
- Performed Technology Risk Management project for one of Thailand's largest banks, with including gap analysis, risk maturity assessment, and training material packs
- Assisted in proposal development, including the PDPA compliance project, the IT compliance project, and the Business Continuity Plan (BCP) project

Trainee, Technology Solution Delivery, Consulting – Internship (January 2020 – March 2020)

- Assisted the project team of SAP GRC in the SAP Automated Tools Authorization project for one of the largest energy companies in Thailand to conduct interview sessions with the client's business units to understand where the roles contain SAP authorization and prepare a gap assessment and single SAP role design
- Bualuang Securities Public Company Limited Thailand

Trainee, Marketing - Internship (June 2019 – July 2019)

- Performed the SWOT analysis of the company and competitors' companies across the industry, created a marketing plan and activities in accordance with the SWOT analysis to propose and present to the counselors
- Performed a financial product project in accordance with innovation and technological change to propose and present to the top management
- Fishsix Mathematics-Physics tutorial school

Mathematics Tutor, Part-time (November 2019 – November 2020)

o Taught mathematics for student Grade 4th-12th